Ashu Karande

Programming Analyst

Pune Maharashtra+91-8999361209

☑ ashukarande05@gmail.comin linkedin.com/in/ashukarande

Summary

A forward thinking developer offering **2 years and 3 months** of experience in building, integrating, testing and supporting web application. Experienced in working with clients, business managers and technical teams for executing concurrent projects.

Ready to work on new technologies.

Insightful knowledge of <u>MVC, C#, VB, SQL Server, SVM,VSS, JQuery, Javascript, ADO.Net,Amcharts.</u> Working knowledge of <u>WCF, Web API.</u>

Basic knowledge of R language.

Skills

Programming and Scripting Languages

ASP.Net MVC, C#, Visual Basic, ADO.Net, JQuery, Javascript

Database and Reporting tool

SQL Server 2008, SQL Server 2014, Oracle, MySQL

Code Control

SVN,VSS

Other

AmCharts, Ajax, WCF, WEb API

Basic Knowledge

R Language, JavaFX, Java Web Services, Core Java, Maven

Awards and Recognition

Distinguished Contributor Award

Mar 2017 - Apr 2017

BNY Mellon India.

Received Distinguished contributor award for implementation of new layout and dashboards.

BOW Award

Sep 2017 - Oct 2017

BNY Mellon India.

BOW award for implementation of new layout, data analysis and dashboards.

Distinguished Contributor Award

Feb 2018 - Feb 2018

BNY Mellon India.

Received Distinguished Contributor Award for 1st JAVAFX project in organization.

Work experience

Achemea Gross Report Automation / AIS Custody Reporting

Feb 2018 - Present

BNY Mellon India.

Applications to manage investment managers.

Achemea Gross Report Automation - Windows Application

- Used selenium for automation.
- Used excel reconciliation for reporting..

AIS Custody Reporting - Web Application.

- Used outlook for mail capture.
- Used R language for predictions.
- Designed UI and also developed scheduler.

<u>Technologies Used</u>: C#, ASP.Net MVC, ADO.Net, SQL Server, JQuery, HTML, Ajax, Bootstrap, Selenium, WCF

Service Director Dashboards / Report Automation / PDF Prime Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

BNY Mellon India.

Applications to manage investment managers.

Report Automation - Windows Application.

• Used excel reconciliation for reporting.

Service Director Dashboard - Web Application.

- Developed for visualization purpose.
- This application will help organization keep transparency between clients and business, which will avoid the losses and manage the things easily.
- It will help keep watch on daily, monthly and yearly issues and supervisor activities.
- R language for data analysis.

PDF Prime - Windows Application

<u>Technologies Used</u>: C#, ASP.Net MVC, ADO.Net, SQL Server, JQuery, HTML, Ajax, Bootstrap, Amcharts, JAVA FX, Web Service

Issue Tracker / Worpoint / PDF Prime Connect

March 2016 - Dec 2017

BNY Mellon India.

Applications to manage domestic as well as international audit.

Issue Tracker - Web Application.

Workpoint - Web Application.

PDF Prime Connect - Windows Application

<u>Technologies Used</u>: C#, ASP.Net MVC, ADO.Net, SQL Server, JQuery, HTML, Ajax, Bootstrap, AmCharts, Web Service, Web API

Education

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

2010 - 2014

Pune University

HSC 2008 - 2010

Pune University

Completed HSC with 60.00 percentage.

Personal Information

Name: Ashu Karande.

Date of Birth: 05 Nov, 1992

Nationality: Indian Gender: Female

Languages Known: English, Hindi, Marathi

Marital Status: Single Passport Valid: YES

Permanent Address: Chinchwad, Pune-019.

Phone Number: +91 8999361209 / +91 9146362907